{
    "id": "0b0eef875f6a49a29651495ef31f3d7a",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The soldiers killed the terrorists by acting ...................... tips from the villagers.",
            "description": "To act on is to take action on the basis of information received.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d216f01282cf41b399ef094007a338b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children acted ................................ the story of Snow White on stage.",
            "description": "To act out is to perform with actions and gestures.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "out",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bbb9d4ac5b7b40a1bed0fbd123696e17"
        },
        {
            "question": "The car has started acting ....................... again. It doesn't start.",
            "description": "To act up is to behave badly.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6ad46476431b4c5ea383d082d370607c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your explanations just don't add ...................",
            "description": "When things add up, they make sense.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2eb7a4c9bcac4c9b869b9c7caf734fed"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mutton or beef does not agree .................................. me.",
            "description": "If something does not agree with you, it has a negative impact on you.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a642af5928524368897e462424815e53"
        },
        {
            "question": "Commercials aimed ........................ children must be banned.",
            "description": "To aim at is to target.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9674da7807ea489ca9b78cfde8bb12db"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must never answer ........................... your elders.",
            "description": "To answer back is to reply rudely to an elderly person.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "back",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0823989a7b1a42f6910aa7a31685983e"
        },
        {
            "question": "",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d79acdfbc1194215bfa57478ee29feb2"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will never manage to argue me .......................",
            "description": "To argue somebody down is to beat them in an argument.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "on",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3de1ae24ee554371b6e93cc77449119f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her children live abroad but they ask ..................... her every day.",
            "description": "To ask after somebody is to inquire about their health.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "after",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d4887fb1256441cfb95c449ee05d7864"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you like her, why don't you ask her ..................... for lunch?",
            "description": "To ask somebody over is to invite them.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "over",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aac5f0c08da8486baa6f69c79bbbeb11"
        },
        {
            "question": "The brave villagers forced the invaders to back ..................................",
            "description": "To back off is to retreat.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "04e36c5fd2944c478afbb045d8e96826"
        },
        {
            "question": "She had promised to lend me some money but backed .................. at the last moment.",
            "description": "To back out of a promise is to fail to keep it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3d04e9d914c54124bdf3d7e9f53f8354"
        }
    ]
}